D
FROM A VIRUS COOKED UP IN A LAB
AND SOMEONE HAS TO ANSWER FOR
IT.
JOHN KIRIAKOU IS A FORMER CIA
OFFICER AND WHISTLE-BLOWER.
DOES THIS JIVE WITH HOW THINGS
ARE DONE AT THE AGENCY, SOMEONE
JUST MAKES A PHONE CALL AND
EVERYTHING CHANGES?
>> UNFORTUNATELY, THIS.
WE SEE THIS KIND OF THING ALL
THE TIME.
AND JESSE, AT THE HEART OF THIS
STORY IS THAT IT'S ALWAYS BEST
TO TELL THE TRUTH.
THE TRUTH ALWAYS COMES OUT.
KENT I WANT TO COMMENT ON THE
WHISTLE-BLOWER.
THIS WAS A VERY BRAVE THING HE
DID.
HE PUT HIS REPUTATION ON THE
LINE TODAY.
HE TOLD THE WORLD EXACTLY WHAT
THE TRUTH WAS.
HE WILL PROBABLY NEVER WORK IN
GOVERNMENT AGAIN BECAUSE OF IT.
BUT NOW WE HAVE AN IDEA OF WHAT
WAS BEING DONE SECRETLY YET IN
OUR NAME.
>> Jesse: AND FAUCI GOT
PARDONED.
SO HE MAY HAVE KILLED 1 MILLION
AMERICANS.
WE DON'T KNOW OF THE EXACT VIRUS
WAS FRANKENSTEINED OUT THAT HE
PAID FOR, BUT STILL, AND THEN HE
JUST WALKS AWAY LIKE NOTHING
HAPPENED?
>> MY COUSIN GEORGE WAS THE
SECOND PERSON IN THE STATE OF
OHIO TO DIE OF COVID BACK IN
VERY EARLY 2020.
THAT DEATH STILL STINGS ALL OF
US IN OUR FAMILY.
AND NOW I CAN'T HELP BUT LOOK AT
DOCTOR FAUCI AND THINK, YOU
LIAR, LOOK WHAT YOU'VE DONE TO
OUR COUNTRY.
AND YOU'RE RIGHT, HE WAS AUTO
PEN RIGHT INTO FREEDOM AND
WEALTH AND UNTOLD RICHES IN HIS
RETIREMENT.
THAT IS UNACCEPTABLE.
>> Jesse: HE WAS PROTECTED AND
SO WAS CHINA WHICH MAKES IT EVEN
WORSE.
AND THIS JUST IN, THIS CIA JUST
RAIDED TULSI GABBARD'S OFFICE.
AGENTS BROUGHT OUT DOZENS OF
BOXES, FILES ON THE JFK
ASSASSINATION, AND MKULTRA, THIS
CIA MIND CONTROL OPERATION,
WHICH SHE WAS IN THE PROCESS OF
DECLASSIFYING.
TODAY'S WHISTLE-BLOWERS SAID IT
DURING THE DEPOSITION AND
CONGRESSWOMAN ANNA PAULINA LUNA
CONFIRMED IT MOMENTS AGO.
>> THE REASON WHY THIS IS
TROUBLING IS LETTER A THERE WAS
AN EXECUTIVE ORDER THAT THE
PRESIDENT HAD DIRECTED THE FULL
DECLASSIFICATION OF JFK BUT THEN
ALSO THE MKULTRA FILES THE CIA
FAMOUSLY HAS SAID THAT ALL
DOCUMENTS WERE RELEASED AND
OTHER DOCUMENTS HAD BEEN
DESTROYED.
SO THESE ARE ALLEGEDLY THOSE
DOCUMENTS THAT APPARENTLY NEVER
EXISTED.
>> Jesse: CAN THE CIA OVERRULE
THE PRESIDENT?
>> NO, THIS CIA CANNOT OVERRULE
THE PRESIDENT.
THE CIA CANNOT EVEN OVERRULE THE
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE.
IN 1975, THE CHURCH COMMITTEE,
WHICH BECAME THE SENATE SELECT
COMMITTEE ON INTELLIGENCE
SPECIFICALLY ORDERED DCI WILLIAM
COLBY TO RELEASE ALL OF THE
MKULTRA FILES.
HE FAMOUSLY WENT BACK TO CIA
HEADQUARTERS AND ORDERED THAT
ALL OF THE FILES BE DESTROYED.
85% OF THEM WERE DESTROYED.
HE WAS HELD IN CONTEMPT OF
CONGRESS AND THEN CIA EMPLOYEES
LINED THE HALLS AND CONTRIBUTED
CASH TO PAY FOR THE FINE THAT HE
WAS ORDERED TO PAY.
WE ONLY KNOW WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT
MKULTRA BECAUSE OF THE 15% OF
THE FILES THAT WERE NOT
DESTROYED.
THESE ARE AMONG THOSE 15% OF THE
FILES.
THEY ARE MANDATED TO BE
DECLASSIFIED.
THE AMERICAN PEOPLE HAVE A RIGHT
TO KNOW WHAT IS IN THESE FILES.
AND THE CIA CAN'T RAID OFFICES,
LEAST OF ALL THE OFFICES OF THE
DIRECTOR OF NATIONAL
INTELLIGENCE.
IT'S JUST-- REAL LIFE IS NOT
SUPPOSED TO WORK THIS WAY, THIS
IS CRAZY.
>> Jesse: THIS IS SOMETHING
OUT OF A MOVIE BUT THE CIA WAS
EXPERIMENTING WITH LSD ON
WILLING AND UNWILLING
PARTICIPANTS DURING THE COLD WAR
FOR INTELLIGENCE OPERATIONS AND
TO EXPLOIT PEOPLE.
AND IT DID NOT GO WELL A LOT OF
THE TIME.
AND THEY THREW IT ALL IN A
WASTEBASKET.
IT NEVER REALLY WORKED.
IS THAT WHY THEY DON'T WANT
ANYBODY TO KNOW ABOUT IT?
>> I THINK THEY DON'T WANT
PEOPLE TO KNOW ANY MORE THAN
WHAT WE KNOW ABOUT FOR EXAMPLE
DOSING INNOCENT CITIZENS OF
SAN FRANCISCO, CALIFORNIA, OR A
SMALL VILLAGE IN FRANCE AND
PUTTING LSD IN THE YEAST AT THE
ONLY BAKERY IN THE VILLAGE JUST
TO SEE IF EVERYBODY IN THE
VILLAGE WOULD GO NUTS, WHICH
THEY DID OF COURSE, OR COMING UP
WITH A PROGRAM IN SAN FRANCISCO
TO HIRE TO DOSE JOHNS AND SEE IF
THEY WOULD COUGH UP THEIR
INNERMOST SECRETS.
RIDICULOUS.
>> Jesse: WELL WE JUST HAVE TO
HIRE SWALWELL.
HE WILL DO PRETTY MU